Lois Lenski Collection
Lois Lenski Collection
- Children's letters
  - Children's letters, April 1951-Oct 1955
    - New Hampshire (Box 12)
    - New Jersey (Box 12)
    - New York (Box 12)
    - North Carolina (Box 12)
    - North Dakota (Box 12)
    - Ohio (Box 12)
    - Oklahoma (Box 12)
    - Oregon (Box 12)
    - Pennsylvania (Box 12)
    - South Carolina (Box 12)
    - South Dakota (Box 12)
    - Tennessee (Box 12)
    - Texas (Box 12)
    - Utah (Box 12)
    - Virginia (Box 12)
    - Washington (Box 12)
    - Washington, D. C. (Box 12)
    - West Virginia (Box 12)
    - Wisconsin (Box 12)
    - Miscellaneous (no state) (Box 12)
  - Children's letters, Nov 1955-Sep 1959
    - Alabama (Box 13)
    - Arizona (Box 13)
    - Arkansas (Box 13)
    - California (Box 13)
    - Connecticut (Box 13)
    - Delaware (Box 13)
    - England (Box 13)
    - Florida (Box 13)
    - Georgia (Box 13)
    - Hawaii (Box 13)
    - Illinois (Box 13)
    - Indiana (Box 13)
    - Iowa (Box 13)
    - Kansas (Box 13)
    - Kentucky (Box 13)
    - Louisiana (Box 13)
    - Massachusetts (Box 13)
    - Michigan (Box 13)
    - Minnesota (Box 13)
    - Mississippi (Box 13)
    - Missouri (Box 13)
    - Maryland (Box 13)
    - Nebraska (Box 13)
    - New Hampshire (Box 13)
    - New Jersey (Box 13)
    - New Mexico (Box 13)
    - New York (Box 14)
    - New York (Box 14)
    - North Africa (Box 14)
    - North Carolina (Box 14)
    - North Dakota (Box 14)
    - Ohio, 2 folders (Box 14)
    - Oklahoma (Box 14)
    - Oregon (Box 14)
    - Pennsylvania (Box 14)
    - Rhode Island (Box 14)
    - South Carolina (Box 14)
    - Tennessee (Box 14)
    - Texas (Box 14)
    - Virginia (Box 14)
    - Washington (Box 14)
    - West Virginia (Box 14)
    - Wisconsin (Box 14)
    - Miscellaneous (no state) (Box 14)
  - Children's letters, Oct 1959-Jul 1963
    - Alabama (Box 15)
    - Arkansas (Box 15)
    - Australia (Box 15)
    - California (Box 15)
    - Colorado (Box 15)
    - Canada (Box 15)
    - Connecticut (Box 15)
    - Delaware (Box 15)
    - Florida (Box 15)
    - Georgia (Box 15)
    - Hawaii (Box 15)
    - Idaho (Box 15)
    - Illinois (Box 15)
    - Indiana (Box 15)
    - Iowa (Box 15)
    - Iowa (Box 15)
    - Kansas (Box 15)
    - Kentucky (Box 15)
    - Louisiana (Box 15)
    - Maryland (Box 15)
    - Massachusetts (Box 15)
    - Michigan (Box 15)
    - Minnesota (Box 16)
    - Mississippi (Box 16)
    - Missouri (Box 16)
    - Montana (Box 16)
    - Nebraska (Box 16)
    - New Jersey (Box 16)
    - New Mexico (Box 16)
    - New York (Box 16)
    - New York (Box 16)
    - North Carolina (Box 16)
    - North Dakota (Box 16)
    - Ohio (Box 16)
    - Oklahoma (Box 16)
    - Oregon (Box 16)
    - Pennsylvania (Box 16)
    - Philippines (Box 16)
    - Rhode Island (Box 16)
    - South Carolina (Box 16)
    - Tennessee (Box 16)
    - Texas (Box 16)
    - Vermont (Box 16)
    - Virginia (Box 16)
    - Washington (Box 16)
    - Washington, D. C. (Box 16)
    - Wisconsin (Box 16)
    - Miscellaneous (no state) (Box 16)
  - Scrapbooks, made for Lois Lenski by children from schools in Florida, Ohio and Minnesota; 3 items (Oversize 4)
- Subject file
  - Biographical material (Box 17)
  - Lois Lenski, An Appreciation, University of North Carolina Press, 1962 (Box 17)
  - Articles about Lenski (Box 17)
  - Photo album, family (Box 17)
  - Lithographs, original, 1932; 4 items (Box 17)
  - Linoleum block prints, 19 items (Box 17)
  - Woodcuts, original, 3 items (Box 17)
  - Illustrations by Lenski (Box 17)
  - Exhibitions (Box 17)
  - Publisher's brochures (Box 17)
  - Notes for art lectures, holograph (Box 17)